Good cake...
What a pitiful sight.
Iorogi.
Kobato.
Dou sureba iin dakke?
Atarimae no kototte itsumo
Muzukashii na
Ureshii toki waratte
Suki na toki ni utaitai dake
Na no ni
Itsuka negai wa kanau to
Demo "itsuka" tte dore kurai?
Machikirenai yo
123! no aizu de ryoute hirogete
Zenshin ni hikari wo atsumete
Doko ni aru no?
Oshiete, watashi ni dekiru koto
Meippai kizu tsuite
Seiippai hashitte
Nan juu kai koronde naite
Sore de mo mada
Akireru kurai
Ashita wo shinjiteru
...Silver Eyes.
Hey! It's Kobato!
Good morning Kobato!
Good morning.
Kobato, can I put a ribbon on your doll?
My doll?
Oh, you mean Ioryogi-san?
Oh hey come on, give me a break.
Yes, please!
How cute!
Yes. Ioryogi-san is happy, too.
What makes you think I'm happy?!
Good morning.
Good morning, Kobato.
Thanks for your help, as always.
Yes.
Well, I've got to go now, Ioryogi-san.
Why does she insist on carrying
that thing around?
It's probably very important to her.
So delicious
Bear's Baumkuchen Shop
Baumkuchen
Baked to perfection
Oh, yes Perfection
Freshly baked by the bear from the woods
You're an eyesore.
Come on, get inside.
Ginsei.
I'll tell you, he's not here.
I know that.
Then what brings you here?
I just want to know what's on his mind.
Why are you asking me?
Never mind.
We appear like this now,
but we are from Ikai.
Why bring that up now?
Well then, what was the
initiative in us being here?
There are four worlds: "Tenkai,"
"Ningenkai," "Chikai" and "Ikai."
The only ones who are not conscious
of there being different worlds
are the humans from "Ningenkai."
In Tenkai there are angels,
who are under God's rule.
Demons follow the Devil's rule in Chikai.
And in Ikai, where we are from, we have our
master, "Kototonushi" to bow down to.
In each world, nonaggression is the rule
of thumb. But look at that fool Iorogi.
Okay, okay, that little bit of a fool Iorogi.
If he hadn't started a war with Tenkai,
we wouldn't all be in this mess.
The reason Iorogi went to war with Tenkai
was because there was something there
that he wanted, no matter what.
But...
He never got it.
That's right. He should've just gone and stolen
it, just like that son of the Devil in Chikai did.
So we end up losing, and the dude gets turned
into a doll for breaking the Nonaggression Act.
I become the bear with a Baumkuchen shop, and
Zuisho gets turned into a silly-looking bird.
Just goes to show that even the amazing
"God" can get fed up at times.
I mean, we got it pretty bad,
but as the mastermind,
he's definitely in the toughest position.
What must Iorogi do to return to Ikai?
Until that girl's wish comes true,
he'll remain in that form,
and he won't be able to return to Ikai.
Wish?
After she has filled her bottle with
broken human hearts she had healed,
then her dream will come true.
Iorogi's job is to help her.
That was his promise to "God".
I have no idea what he's thinking.
Well, one thing I can say though, is that
since Iorogi arrived at Ningenkai...
You see, since he started hanging
around with that girl, he's changed.
Just leave him alone for awhile.
Come on, have some of this.
Darn.
He doesn't know what he's missing.
If my old friends saw me like this, they'd cry!
Oh?
Come and get me if you can.
Kobato. Good morning.
Domoto!
What brings you to the kindergarten?
I came to see Fujimoto.
Huh?
Time for lunch, everybody.
Wash your hands and get inside!
Okay!
Fujimoto.
What are you doing here?
I came to get you. I think it would be
good to attend today's seminar.
I'm not going.
But you took it because you wanted to.
Um... What's a seminar?
It's a class at university.
Oh. University studies.
Mhm.
You missed the last one too.
You really should go today.
Please go, Fujimoto!
I can't. I'm too busy.
Fujimoto!
Kobato...
Don't worry about it. I have a plan.
Huh?
That's enough for today.
You've got an important seminar
in the afternoon, don't you?
Ms. Sayaka
I've helped out here on a number of occasions.
I realized something on one of those occasions.
The children will be taking a nap in the
afternoon anyway and Kobato is here to help.
We'll be all right.
However...
Fujimoto.
You always are a tremendous help.
But you know, I don't want you
skipping classes at university.
Will you do that?
Sure.
He listens to her.
He'll do whatever Ms. Sayaka says. Only her.
I cannot be seen wearing this dreamy girly thing!
Bye for now, Kobato. I'll visit you again.
Yes. Please come again.
See you.
Have a nice afternoon!
Kobato is ready to cover for Fujimoto too!
Wow, that's wonderful!
Darn, I can't get it off! That Fujimoto!
He tied it too tight!
Thank you so much for today, Kobato.
It really helped to have you around.
N-No problem!
Now go home and get some rest, okay?
Yes!
That ribbon looks very nice on little Ioryogi.
"Little" Ioryogi?
Yes! See you tomorrow!
It's still a bit hot, isn't it?
It's cooler where there is dirt.
It feels good doesn't it, Ioryogi-san?
Hey! What are you doing?!
You're all squished right here.
You know why?
Because you're hungry?
Kobato...
The seasons continue to change, you know.
You didn't come here to help out at
the kindergarten, did you?
But today, Fujimoto wasn't there so I
wanted to do my best to cover for him.
You do what you're supposed to be doing
before talking about such things!
Unless you quickly fill this bottle,
your wish isn't going to come true.
Ginsei...
Is he your friend, Ioryogi-san?
Ioryogi-san?!
So she's the one!
Kobato!
Ioryogi-san?
Oh, could that be?
Man... if you break that...
I'll never forgive you...!
Why is that?
Why do you stay in Ningenkai for
so long, looking like that?
I've got things to do.
Master Genko!
Zuisho! Would you quit flapping around in the
shop? You'll get feathers into the dough!
Well sir, I'm a bird now. I can't help it.
All right, all right.
So what is it?
Oh that's right!
There's a dangerous situation developing
between that violent, selfish,
turned into some sort of doll guy
and the problem maker who used
to work for him, sir!
Oh. Is that so.
Huh? That's it?
Well then take this.
Give it to the one that loses. For condolence.
Are you going to let them go at it?
They're really going to cause a ruckus.
Nobody can stop those two.
The guy was originally picked up by Iorogi.
It was Iorogi who named him for his silver eyes.
"Gin" for silver and "sei" for being.
I thought the name lacked thought,
so I told him to reconsider,
but then we ended up getting into a fist fight.
I'm not surprised.
So he was picked up and given a name.
And that's why he dwells on Iorogi issues.
They're going to have to settle
this one themselves.
Return that bottle.
Get it yourself, "Mister Ioryogi".
Well?! You want to get barbecued right here?!
You don't expect to keep me down for
long in your present state, do you?
Why you!
You're a sorry sight. Your looks and your name.
"Ioryogi"? Give me a break.
Io... ryo?
I-o-ro-gi!
I-o-ryo-gi!
I'm telling you, it's Iorogi!
I-o-ryo-gi?
No! It's Ioryogi... huh?
Right. Ioryogi-san!
But you know, I like that name I have now.
Anyway, give back the bottle.
Tell me you're coming back to Ikai.
I told you, I've got things to do. I'm not
returning... until I see it through.
It's about "the wish" isn't it?
What do you see in her?
She has put me through
so much trouble already.
Then get rid of her.
What?
If she doesn't exist, there are no more wishes.
Then you should be able to return to Ikai.
In the past, you would have done that.
You're probably right.
She's really clumsy and has no common sense.
Kobato is ready!
She always thinks of herself last.
She'll bend over backwards and exhaust
herself doing things for others
that she hasn't even been asked to do.
But you know...
That ridiculous personality of hers...
I kind of like that about her.
I can't bear to hear of it.
Watch it! My insides are going to come out!
If "the bottle" does not get filled,
the wish will not come true.
Ginsei!
In that case, if there was no bottle...
Don't do it!
I cannot bring myself to obey
you the way you are now!
Ginsei!
I'm begging you!
Please give me back the bottle.
Without that, Kobato...
Please.
Since he started hanging around
with that girl, he's changed.
You're begging me?
You would never have said that before.
Fulfill your objectives quickly.
Ginsei...
Ioryogi-san!
Kobato!
Kohaku!
What's the matter?
Ioryogi-san is gone!
I saw Ioryogi-san at Sakura Park.
Come and get me, if you can.
Why, you!
He seemed to be having so much fun
playing tag with his friend from Ikai,
so I didn't say hello.
Sakura Park? Thank you very much!
You're welcome.
Damn! What a useless body!
But I've come this far, so...
You're hurting me, idiot!
Ioryogi-san!
Ioryogi-san! Where are you?!
Hey!
Fujimoto?!
Here.
Ioryogi-san!
What a relief, Ioryogi-san.
Thank you very much for
finding Ioryogi-san for me.
Ah, right.
Ioryogi-san got himself lost.
Lost?
I'm so glad nothing happened to him.
Is that doll that important to you?
Yes! Ioryogi-san and I are always together!
This is good!
That bear is really thoughtful.
It looks very nice on you!
Why, you...
Ioryogi-san.
Thank you so much for getting the bottle back.
I'm very thankful.
Dobato!
Minus two-hundred points!
What?!
How could you let that precious
bottle be stolen! Get a grip!
I'm sorry.
What is it, "fancy day" today?! Why does
everyone want to tie a ribbon to me?!
Ioryogi-san and I are always together!
Ioryogi-san?
What is it?
I still think that ribbon looks good on you.
It does not look good on me!
That's not true! Look! Tie another
one and you look even...
No, stop it!
And tie another one, and...
I'm telling you to cut that out!
Oh? Then let's try one more.
Hito wa mina tonde mitai no ni
Juuryoku ni damasareterunda
Dare mo honto wa toberunda yo
Ano ko ga anna ni kanashisou na no wa
Jibun no kage wo
Dokoka ni wasurete kichatta kara kamo
Sore nara
"Arigatou," tte kimi ni ietara
"Arigatou," tte kimi ga waraeba
Ittari kitari ureshiku naru
Kimi ga shiawase ni naru
Shinpai nante iranai yo
Issho ni iru kara
Ureshikuttemo namida ga deru nante
Fushigi da
Next episode
...Angel and the Protector.
Fushigi da
Next episode
...Angel and the Protector.